Nighttime and Idol
Yes, that's right.
I have sent you 3 things that Aira-san would like to do in the future...
Yes, sir.
How did you feel when you tried them?
It was something I really wanted to do.
I've been talking about it more and more and more
I'm getting excited on my own.
It's like I feel like I've already done it even though I haven't done it yet.
It was a lot of fun.
It's great. It's a dream come true.
There are so many more things I want to do.
I'm sure there are many more things I want to do.
Now, in the midst of all this...
Mr. Aida and Mr. Ameflash
Yes
I know you've been busy with your activities
I'd like to make an announcement here.
Yes, we are...
We are now distributing a digital single
Sneakers Delight Ameflash version is now available!
The reason why it's called "Ame-Flash Version" is because we used to work with a group called 3D Junior.
Sneakers Delight is a song that we used to play as a group called 3D Junior.
We've re-recorded the song and released it as a 4 member version of AmeFlash.
It's a little different from the previous version, with a more mature feel and a cooler singing style.
So please give it a listen if you like.
But if you pay attention to the lyrics, they're lyrics that can be sung by people of today's age.
That's right.
When I was in 3B Jr.
I think we were singing and dancing to this song when we were 3B JUNIOR.
The choreography is also more powerful.
The choreography is more powerful, and when I listen to the lyrics
I feel like it's more like AmeFlash now.
I also feel the music is more stylish
It's more stylish and cool
I think it's perfect for today's AmeFlash.
I think you'll enjoy listening to it.
And in March, we have a lot of live performances.
We're going to have a joint concert with Miss Mercy at the Port of Yusu.
We'll be performing at LaLaPort Toyosu.
It's called "Kakeru Mercy" and it's going to be held on Sunday, March 3rd.
I'm going to be performing at Miss Mercy's concert.
I'm looking forward to it.
You're looking forward to it?
There are a lot of senior members here, so I've always been in the position of a junior member.
I'm super happy to be invited to Miss Mercy's concert.
It's a little disconcerting to be the junior, but Miss Merci really likes AmeFlash.
Every time I see her, she tells me that she respects me a lot.
I'm so happy to be able to perform with these girls.
After that, we're going to do
On Friday, March 15, we will be performing at the EX Theater Roppongi!
This EX Theatre Roppongi is also the same venue that we performed at when we were 3B Junior.
At that time, it didn't sell out and we couldn't fill the venue.
But since we were standing in a big group, we didn't get a lot of spotlight,
So, I want to do it again, and I also want to make the show enjoyable for the newcomers and old supporters of ours.
I also want to make it a live show that you can enjoy, so please come and enjoy the show.
We will be performing in Osaka and Nagoya on Thursday, March 21 at a venue called Umeda Shangri-La in Osaka, and the next day, March 22, at a venue called Bottom Line in Aichi.
The next day, March 22, we will be playing at a venue called Bottom Line in Aichi.
I'm really happy to be able to go to Osaka and Nagoya like this every year, and I want people to know about AmeFlash,
Last year we did a free live tour, and we hope that people who can't come to Tokyo can come to our free live tour,
I'm really happy to be able to see those people who can't come to Tokyo, or those who like us in Osaka or Nagoya.
Lastly, I would like to say a few words to the fans who have been supporting us.
I would like you to say goodbye to the camera with a message for the fans who have been supporting you.
Thank you very much for your support.
This year, I would like to improve even more than last year.
This year, I would like to make our live performances and social networking services even more powerful than last year,
I hope to deliver contents that will cheer you up,
I hope that you will enjoy our live performances and social networking services.
So, that's all for now. Bye bye.
This program is sponsored by
Mr. AmeFlash
Yuki-san
Mr. Ryo
Eri Eri-san
This program was provided by Take-chan.
Thank you very much!
Sent to you courtesy of Take-chan